# Katharine Gorecki

500 West Ave PH24 Norwalk, CT 06850 T: 203.506.8228

E: katharinemgi@gmail.com



# Summary

With 13 years of experience, I have enjoyed a career in fashion and most recently, in fashion tech. I have held various styling and management positions that have focused on different aspects of the business including new store openings, clienteling, customer service, human resources, and merchandising. I am looking to join a company with which I have the ability to grow, and in turn, I can be a part of its growth.

# Experience

## Stylist/ Brand Manager, PS Dept

New York, NY — 2015 - Present

- Oversee the business of luxury brands, which includes CHANEL, Dior, Gucci, and Hermés.
- Generated \$6.6 million in sales in my 2.5 years with PS Dept.
- Provide exceptional service to our clients which helps result in a 36% overall conversion, >50% member conversion and 63% retention rate.
- Contribute in the planning of successful initiatives such as fee structure and membership roll out.
- Meet with developers to provide feedback and help create updates on how to make the app more efficient and scalable.
- Create my own systems to help manage each stores inventory and the 800+ requests we field on average per week.
- Assist in writing and editing copy for emails and campaigns.

#### ASM/ Store Manager, Vince

New York, NY — 2014 - 2015

- Led the opening of and managed Vince's premier men's store.
- Exceeded plan every month, trending +20% for the year
- Trained the staff in order to take over and ensure the continued success of the business when Lleft.

#### Men's Specialist/ Supervisor, Theory

New York, NY — 2012 - 2014

- Managed the men's business of the flagship location resulting in sales 30+% above budget.
- Generated roughly \$1 million in a year.
- Worked closely with corporate partners in order to ensure the success of the men's business.
- Pioneered the use of PS Dept. personal shopping app for Theory.
- Provided product knowledge and fit knowledge for sales associates.

## Sales Manager, Juicy Couture

New York, NY — 2010 - 2012

- Supervised the sales floor of a \$25 million flagship location, with a focus on training and development.
- Motivated a sales team of 15 associates and 3 specialists to reach their weekly goals.
- Led the clienteling initiative for our store and conduct training classes.
- Maintained visual standards to the highest degree for our flagship location.

# General Manager, Gilly Hicks/ Hollister Co - Abercrombie & Fitch

Multiple Cities, Greater NY — 2004 - 2009

- Led a staff of 8 managers, 1 full-time stock, and 122 part-time associates.
- Managed opening of the second Gilly Hicks store location in the Nation (new concept by A&F) along with other new store openings.
- Recruited, interviewed, hired, and trained a staff of 150 employees on many aspects of the store, including but not limited to product knowledge, operating tools used to support merchandising systems, and loss prevention recovery tactics.
- Sporadically managed multiple Gilly Hicks store locations nationwide through setting examples and conference call game planning
- Served as a liaison between headquarters and stores by reporting analysis and results from monitoring and evaluating store sales performance through daily audits.
- Conducted weekly management meeting concerning business successes, concerns, and risk management.

### Education

## The University of Connecticut

**Bachelor of Science in Human Development and Family Studies** 

Recipient of the University of Connecticut Leadership Scholarship.

#### Skills

- Brand Development
- Recruiting and Hiring
- Loss Prevention
- Clienteling
- Scheduling
- Merchandising
- Customer Experience
- Training and Development

#### References

Available upon request.